Boomerang Video Games Rental Online - Play more Pay less                          

This item has been added to your basket.  

Our website uses cookies and by using the site you agree to this. [Learn more here.](https://www.boomerangrentals.co.uk/privacy.php) [X](#)

    * **Information**

    * **Category**
    
    * **Genres**
    
    * **Age**

    * **Category**
    
    * **Genres**
    
    * **Age**

    * **Category**
    
    * **Genres**
    
    * **Age**

    * **Category**
    
    * **Genres**
    
    * **Age**

    * **Category**
    
    * **Genres**
    
    * **Age**

    * **Category**
    
    * **Genres**
    
    * **Age**

    * **Category**
    
    * **Genres**
    
    * **Age**

    * **Category**
    
    * **Genres**
    
    * **Age**

    * **Category**
    
    * **Genres**
    
    * **Age**

    * **Category**
    
    * **Genres**
    
    * **Age**

[Home](https://www.boomerangrentals.co.uk/ "Boomerang Rentals") »

Privacy

Privacy

**Privacy Policy**  
  
Boomerang (a trading name of Boomerang Video Ltd, contact details at the bottom of this policy) recognises that your privacy is very important to you and that it is your right to control your personal information. We know that providing personal information is an act of trust and we take that trust seriously. Boomerang will never sell, rent or otherwise disclose any of your personal information, including your Email address, to any third party without your consent. Unless you give us specific consent to act otherwise, the following policies will govern how Boomerang handles the personal information that you provide to us.

**The purpose for holding your data**

We hold only the personal data we need as follows;

1) To fulfil the service you have signed up for.  The legal basis for holding this data is that we require this data to fulfil the contract between you and us.

2) Where you have given us permission, via Opting In, we may use the email address you provided to email offers and other marketing promotions to you.

Personal data means "any information relating to an identifiable person who can be directly or indirectly identified in particular by reference to an identifier". As such we hold your First Name, Last Name, Postal and Billing Card (if different) address, phone number (if you provided it) and Email address.

**Third Parties**

We will never pass your personal data on to other companies (Data Controllers) for marketing purposes.

We may from time to time, use a third-party review service and this third party will only receive the data necessary to provide this service.

If you have Opted In to email marketing, we may use a third-party email service provider, who will also only receive the data necessary to fulfil this role on our behalf.

Your payment card details are held securely by Sagepay, our Level 1 payment provider.

We will never transfer your data outside of the EU.

**Hold long we hold your data for**

We hold your data for the following periods;

* 3 years after the last transaction by you, where all rentals (for rental accounts) have been successfully received OR
* For 6 years if that customers account has become delinquent

**Your rights regarding your data**

Your rights are detailed below, together with our policy pertaining to each right;

_The right to be informed_     

This is provided for under our Privacy Policy on the website.

_The right of access_

Your is visible in the My Account/Manage account section of the website.

Alternatively, if you do not have access to the site, this information can be provided on email within 1 month of the request.

_The right to rectification_     

Your data can be rectified in the My Account/Manage account section of the website.

Alternatively, if you do not have access to the site, this information can be provided on email within 1 month of the request.

_The right to erase_

This is subject to submitting a request, and we will respond on a case by case basis.

_The right to restrict processing_

This is subject to submitting a request, and we will respond on a case by case basis.

_The right to data portability_

Your data is visible in the My Account/Manage account section of the website and can be copy and pasted from there.

Alternatively, you do not have access to the site, this information can be provided on email in CSV format within 1 month of the request.

**Your right to make a complaint**

You have the right to make a complaint to the Information Commissioners Office (ICO) if you feel that your data is not held or processed as you expected.

You can contact the ICO here;

https://ico.org.uk/concerns/

**Automated decision making or profiling**

We do not hold or process your personal data in any way that constitutes this type of activity.

**Information storage**  
  
All information you provide to us is stored in the UK only on secure servers that are protected in secure facilites including firewall protection. 

**We do not store Credit Card details, these are held by our level 1 PCI compliant Payment Service Provider.**  
  
**Cookies**  
  
Boomerang uses cookies to help speed up the login process and for security purposes. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your web browser from a web server and stored on your computer.  
  
Boomerang may store up to two types of cookie on your computer:  
i. A unique ID is stored in a permanent cookie so that you do not need to retype information every time you visit our site.  
ii. Your web browser's session identification is stored in a temporary cookie to help prevent unauthorised use of your account.  
More detailed information on cookies may be found in the Help section of your web browser.

Boomerangs website uses cookies which are small text files that we store on your computer. For more information about cookies you can visit many sites including [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).  
  
EU Privacy Law now requires that we provide you with information about our cookies so that you can make an informed decision about whether you want to allow us to continue using them while you browse our site. Please be aware that some of our cookies are 'strictly necessary' for the operation of the site such as storing login statuses and managing the shopping basket and checkout process and preventing us using them will prevent you from using this site.

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Duration | Use | Information on what it does |
| BoomerangCoUkAuth | 1 year | Functionality | Boomerang uses this cookie to remember your log in details when you click on the "remember me" option on the log in page |
| \_\_zlcmid | 1 year | Functionality | We use Zopim to provide live customer service chat on our Site. Zopim requires two cookies: the first cookie stores Zopim Live Chat ID to identify the device during visits. The second stores user’s preference to disable Live Chat. |
| \_\_zlcprivacy | 1 year | Functionality | Zopim. This cookie remembers the users’ choice in disabling the chat service |
| PHPSESSID | session only | Functionality | To store a simple message when a form is submitted that can be displayed on a different page. For example, if an enquiry form is completed incorrectly, a message will be stored and presented to the user to indicate the errors in the submission.    When an enquiry form is submitted successfully, a message is stored and presented to the user thanking them for their enquiry. No personal information is stored in this cookie. |
| WRUID | Persistent | Analytics | This cookie name is commonly associated with analytics service provider ClickTale. This cookie is used to anonymously identify a visitor of the website for the purpose of enabling the ClickTale software to track such visitor’s actions across the client’s website. |
| \_\_CT\_Data | Persistent | Analytics | A cookie associated with analytics service provider ClickTale. According to the company this cookie is used to count the number of page views or visits of an the anonymous visitor to the site. |
| \_\_utma | 2 years | Analytics | Google. This cookie keeps track of the number of times a visitor has been to the site, when their first visit was, and when their last visit occurred. |
| \_\_utmb | 30 mins | Analytics | Google. Holds timestamp of the exact moment in time when a visitor first visits the site. |
| \_\_utmc | Session only | Analytics | Google. Holds timestamp of the exact moment in time when a visitor leaves the site. |
| \_\_utmt | 10 mins | Analytics | Google. Used to throttle the request rate for the service - limiting the collection of data on high traffic sites. It expires after 10 minutes |
| \_\_utmz | 6 months | Analytics | Google. Keeps track of where the visitor came from, what search engine they used, what link was clicked on, what keyword they used, and where in the world they are when they accessed the website. |
| k\_push8 | 21 days | Analytics | Kampyle. A cookie that retains the 21 day invitation opt-out time limit. This is set if / when a user declines a proactive feedback push invitation |
| k\_visit | 1 year | Analytics | Kampyle. Counts the number of user visits |
| push\_time\_start | Session only | Analytics | The time and date that the push invitation was triggered |
| session\_start\_time | session only | Analytics | Kampyle. The time and date that the push invitation was triggered |
| ki\_r | 5 Years | Analytics | KissInsights. Manage pop up survey functionality |
| ki\_s | 5 Years | Analytics | KissInsights. Manage pop up survey functionality |
| ki\_t | 5 Years | Analytics | KissInsights. Manage pop up survey functionality |
| ki\_u | 5 Years | Analytics | KissInsights. Manage pop up survey functionality |

**Information sharing and disclosure**  
  
Boomerang is committed to protecting your personal information. We will not disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent except where:  
a. Boomerang is required by law to disclose information to third parties.  
b. The service is necessary for the performance of our operations ie. mail delivery, review services, hosting services, protecting us from fraud, and payment of your account.  
c. Boomerang buys or sells subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions customer information is one of the transferred assets, but would remain subject to the commitments made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy or equivalent.  
Companies and individuals registered in the Boomerang Affiliate Program may receive aggregate information about customers that they direct to Boomerang through links on their website. No personally identifiable information is provided to affiliate members ; the information collected from our affiliates is used strictly for the affiliates program and will not be used for general marketing purposes.  
  
Boomerang also provides analyses of our customers in the aggregate to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties. We do this so that we and our business partners, such as Facebook, can understand you better, and so we can keep bringing you first-rate services. We may also disclose, on an anonymous basis, literal statements made by our customers. At no time, however, will we disclose personal information about specific customers.

**Security and prevention against loss, misuse or alteration of information**

Linked websites are not under the control of Boomerang and we are not responsible for the conduct of companies linked to our website. Before disclosing your personal information on any other website we advise you to examine their terms and conditions of use. As a subscriber you have certain rights under the General Data Protection Regulation. You have the right to be told what personal information we hold about you on our database. Should you wish to exercise that right, or if you have any questions concerning the Boomerang privacy policy please write to us at: Boomerang, 5 Jupiter House, Callerva Park, Aldermarston, Reading, Berks, RG7 8NN.  
  
Boomerang has implemented technology and security features, as well as strict internal guidelines, to safeguard the privacy of your personal information from unauthorised access or improper use. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available.  
  
For transmitting your personal information to us, we use a secure server with a 128-bit SSL certificate from Thawte which encrypts all of your personal information. This encryption process ensures that the information you give us is protected against unauthorised use.  
While we make every effort to ensure that your information is secure on our system, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.  
  
Your Boomerang account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. You can play an important role in keeping your personal information secure by maintaining the confidentiality of your password used on the Boomerang website. We recommend that you change your password from time to time for additional security. Please advise us immediately if there is any unauthorised use of your account by any other Internet user or any other breach of security.  
  
Access authorisation is granted to key Boomerang (Boomerang Video Ltd.) staff only. Backups are run to prevent loss of information, and our Internet servers are housed in secure facilities.  
  
**Your ability to edit and cancel your account**  
  
You can access My Account from every page on the site to update and correct the personal details that we gathered when you subscribed. You must be logged in to access this information. All information is password-protected so no one can access the information but you.  
  
If you decide to cancel your Boomerang subscription, your account will be deactivated immediately. However we are required to retain your information for accounting and taxation purposes.  
  
**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
  
From time to time, Boomerang will review and may edit this policy in accordance with potential changes to our business and as required by law. Boomerang reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy at any time.  
  
**Contact details**  
  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact Boomerang:  
  
Boomerang Video Ltd  
Attention: Privacy Officer  
5 Jupiter House, Calerva Park, Aldermarston, Reading, Berks, RG7 8NN.  
Email: customersupport@Boomerangrentals.co.uk  
  
Boomerang (a registered trademark) is owned and operated by Boomerang Video Ltd Registered No: 5377400; Registered Office: 5 Jupiter House, Calerva Park, Aldermarston, Reading, Berks, RG7 8NN..  
This version last updated 3rd May 2018

Home

Our Service

Legal

Help

Follow Us

Newsletters  

All trademarks, logos, images, product and company names referred to on this website are the property of their respective owners.
